Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 9 and District 9 Locals, 1936-1990s UE.4.1.9
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 9 Locals, 2.
  - Local 902
    - Local 902 Outgoing Correspondence, April 8, 1940-July 23, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 25)
      - Rice to Matles Regarding Phelps Dodge Negotiations, March 17, 1941; 9.
      - Rice to Matles Regarding Phelps Dodge Negotiations, March 17, 1941; 10.
      - Rice Telegram to Matles Regarding Phelps Dodge Seperate Charter, August 9, 1941; 11.
      - Rice Telegram to Matles Regarding Unemployment, August 22, 1941; 12.
      - Rice Telegram to Matles Regarding Fingerprinting, September 20, 1941; 13.
      - Rice to Paul Williams Regarding Phelps Dodge Grievances, September 22, 1941; 14.
      - Rice Telegram to Matles Regarding Phelps Dodge Negotiations, October 15, 1941; 15.
      - Rice to WIlliams Regarding Phelps Dodge Negotiations, October 21, 1941; 16.
      - Rice Telegram to Matles Regarding Phelps Dodge Negotiations, 17-18.
    - Local 902 Outgoing Correspondence, June 22, 1938-May 4, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 26)
      - Clarence Scheweyer Telegram to Julius Emspak Regarding White Collar Workers Bowser Organization, June 8, 1944; 1.
      - Andrew Schorr to Emspak Regarding Per Capita and Officers, June 22, 1938; 2.
      - Schorr to Emspak Regarding Amalgamation, June 28-July 6, 1938; 3-4.
      - Schorr to James Carey Regarding Horton Closed Shop, February 23, 1939; 5.
      - Schorr to Carey Regarding Horton Union Label, September 18, 1940; 6.
      - Schorr to Matles Regarding Horton Union Label, October 18, 1940; 7.
      - Al Sinnigen to Emspak Regarding Finances, May 4, 1945; 8.
      - Sinnigen to Emspak Regarding Veterans and Dues, June 22, 1945; 9.
      - Sinnigen to Emspak Regarding Wages, November 19, 1945; 10.
      - John Stover to Carey Regarding Capehart Negotiations and Marion Farnsworth Organization, June 6, 1939; 11.
      - Paul Walborn to Matles Regarding Staff Members and Fort Wayne, January 9, 1943; 12.
      - Walborn to Matles Regarding Staff Members, January 30-February 6, 1943; 13-14.
      - Walborn to UE Regarding Officers, September 15, 1943; 15.
    - Local 902 Reports of Financial Secretary, November 1936-July 1938 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Local 902 Monthly Statements, May-October 1936 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Local 902 Per Capita Report, May-July 1949 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Local 902 Convention Credentials, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 30)
      - Mathias Vonderhaar, 1949; 1.
      - Herman Egly, 1949; 2.
      - James Pascoe, 1949; 3.
      - Viola Pasco, 1949; 4.
      - Elizabeth Ulvey, 1949; 5.
    - Local 902 Notices, Ledger and Statement, 1936-1949 (Box 4, Folder 31)
      - Notice of Delinquency, 1938; 1.
      - Dues Ledger, 1936-1939; 2.
      - Financial Statement with Pascoe Memo, 1947; 3.
      - Local Fourth Quarter Quarterly Audit, 1948; 4.
      - Local Third Quarter Quarterly Audit, 1949; 5.
    - Local 902 News Bulletin to Local 902 Member Publications, April 7-August 8, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Local 902 Shop News, November 18, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Local 902 Pamphlets, May 2, 1942-May 9, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 34)
      - Dedication Program, May 2, 1942; 1.
      - Eleven Losses Regarding Factionalism, May 9, 1949; 2.
    - Local 902 Leaflets, November 10, 1948-June 15, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 35)
      - Frankly Jim We Need More Money Regarding Factionalism, November 10, 1948; 1.
      - Why Do the Pascoes Red-Bait, March 8, 1949; 2.
      - Attention Regarding Factionalism, March 11, 1949; 3.
      - As You Well Know Regarding Factionalism, March 22, 1949; 4.
      - Election June 15, Regarding Perfection Biscuit and Bakery Workers Inter-union Rivalry, June 2, 1949; 5.
      - Attention! Regarding Perfection Bisciut and Baker Workers Inter-union Rivalry, June 1949; 6.
      - Election Today Regarding Perfection Biscuit and Bakery Workers Inter-union Rivalry, June 15, 1949; 7.
    - Local 902 Newspaper Clippings, February 1939-March 1949 (Box 4, Folder 36)
      - Nicholas Heads UP New $5,00,000 Farnsworth, February 1939; 1.
      - Farnsworth Stock Approved, March 24, 1939; 2.
      - Marion Plant's Sale Approved, March 24, 1939; 3.
      - UE District Files Motions In Court Here News Sentinel, March 18, 1949; 4.
      - Officers of UE District Take Union Row to Court Fort Wayne Journal-Gazette, March 18, 1949; 5.
      - Local Autonomy in Labor Union at Strike Fort Wayne News Sentinell, March 18, 1949; 6.
      - UE 902 Decision Fort Wayne News Sentinel, March 29, 1949; 7.
      - Temporary Injunction Granted in Union Tiff, March 29, 1949; 8.
      - UERW Group Wins at Horton, 9.
    - Local 902 Van Arnam Furniture Workers Transfers, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 37)
      - Joseph Persily to Joseph Pascoe, 1938; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Pascoe, July 16, 1938; 2.
    - Local 902 Factionalism and Audit, January 5-27, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 38)
      - James Carey Telegram to Bertha Owens, January 5, 1940; 1.
      - Bertha Scott Telegram to Carey, January 6, 1940; 2.
      - George Crance to Scott, January 8, 1940; 3.
      - Scott to Carey, January 8, 1940; 4.
      - Andrew Schorr to Scott, January 27, 1940; 5.
      - Trustees Statement, January 27, 1940; 6.
    - Local 902 Horton Union Label, October 23-24, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 39)
      - James Carey to A. E. Askerberg, October 23, 1940; 1.
      - Robert Cowdrill Telegram to James Carey, October 23, 1940; 2.
      - Carey Telegram to Askerberg, October 24, 1940; 3.
    - Local 902 Perfection Bisciut Strikes, March 20-June 6, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 40)
      - Edwin Beal Telegram to James Carey, March 20, 1941; 1.
      - Beal to Carey, January 6, 1941; 2.
    - Local 902 Factionalism, Finances and Seperate Charter, June 15, 1944-February 17, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 41)
      - J. M. Serrano to Local 902 Executive Board, June 15, 1944; 1.
      - John Gojack to Julius Emspak, August 4, 1944; 2.
      - Emspak to Gojack, August 9,1944; 3.
      - Elizabeth Moore to Emspak, August 11-September 8,1944; 4-6.
      - Petition, December 4, 1944; 7.
      - Moore to Emspak, December 11, 1944; 8.
      - Emspak to Gojack, December 13, 1944; 9.
      - Moore to Emspak, January 2, 1944-January 20, 1945; 10-12.
      - Moore to David Rosston, February 17, 1945; 13.
      - Moore to Emspak, February 17, 1945; 14.
    - Local 902 Factionalism, Finances and Seperate Charter, February 21-July 23, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 42)
      - Report of 902 Committee with February 21, 1945, Robert Rice Letter to Julius Emspak and December 29, 1945, Finance Statement, 1.
      - Albert Olson to Emspak, February 21, 1945; 2.
      - Elizabeth Moore to Emspak, February 24, 1945; 3.
      - Moore to David Ratner, April 7, 1945; 4.
      - Olson to Ratner, May 18-June 4, 1945; 5-6.
      - Emspak Sectetary to Olson, July 23, 1945; 7.
    - Local 902 Pascoes Factionalism, October 28, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 43)
      - John Gojack to All Locals with Old and New Contract, October 28, 1946; 1.
    - Local 902 Pascoes Factionalism, November 18, 1946-September 30, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 44)
      - Petition with November 25, 1946, Julius Emspak to John Gojack, November 18, 1946; 1.
      - Viola Pascoe to Carl Sanford, January 17, 1947; 2.
      - Pascoe to Doyle, September 2, 1947; 3.
      - Lester O'Connor to Local 902, March 30, 1948; 4.
      - O'Connor to Local 902 Executive Board, April 20, 1948; 5.
      - James Pascoe to Union Members, July 9, 1948; 6.
      - Pascoe to O'Connor, July 13, 1948; 7.
      - Gojack to Emspak with Newspaper Clippings and Pascoe Letter to All Union Members, July 21, 1948; 8.
      - Gojack to Emspak, July 31, 1948; 9.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Pascoe, August 3, 1945; 10.
      - Petition, August 3, 1948; 11.
      - O'Connor to Gojack, September 17, 1948; 12.
      - Memo on O'Connor Appeal, September 24, 1948; 13.
      - District 9 Minutes Excerpt, September 24, 1948; 14.
      - Emspak to Stanley Lorey with Summary, September 30, 1948; 15.
    - Local 902 Pascoes Factionalism, November 12, 1948-February 24, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 45)
      - Ernest DeMaio to Albert Fitzgerald, November 12, 1948; 1.
      - Report From Loney and DeMaio, December 10, 1948; 2.
      - Decision of General Executive Board, December 10, 1948; 3.
      - Memo on Pascoes, 1948; 4.
      - Appeal of Pascoes to General Executive Board, 1948; 5.
      - James Pascoe to Julius Emspak, January 28, 1949; 6.
      - Elizabeth Moore to Emspak, February 6-19, 1949; 7-8.
      - Emspak to Moore with January 28, 1949, Pascoe Letter to Moore, February 23, 1949; 9.
      - Moore to Emspak, February 24, 1949; 10.
    - Local 902 Pascoes Factionalism, March 3-28, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 46)
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Ernest DeMaio, March 3, 1949; 1.
      - Robert Rice to Local 902 Members, March 8, 1949; 2.
      - Viola Pasco to Local 902 Members, March 9, 1949; 3.
      - Rice to Local 902 Members, March 11, 1949; 4.
      - DeMaio to Local 902 Members, March 11, 1949; 5.
      - Elizabeth Moore to David Scribner, March 12, 1949; 6.
      - General Executive Board Action with Loney and DeMaio Report, March 18, 1949; 7.
      - Moore to Julius Emspak, March 19, 1949; 8.
      - Lester O'Connor to Local 902 Members, 9.
      - Court Order, March 28, 1949; 10.
    - Local 902 Pascoes Factionalism, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 47)
      - Petition, June 6, 1949; 1.
      - Mathias Vonderhaar to Bernard McHugh, June 8, 1949; 2.
      - James Pascoe to Perfection Bisciut, June 18, 1949; 3.
      - Robert Rice to James Matles, June 20, 1949; 4.
      - Lester O'Connor to Local 902 Executive Board, July 8, 1949; 5.
      - Memo, August 22, 1949; 6.
      - Court Brief with Financial Statement, 1949; 7.
    - Local 902 Correspondence, Study, List, Minutes, and Resolution, June 24, 1936-January 25, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 48)
      - Study of Recently Organized Locals, June 24, 1936; 1.
      - James Pascoe to Julius Emspak Regarding National Labor Relations Board and Essex Wire Firings, June 20, 1938; 2.
      - Wage Rates, February 21, 1939; 3.
      - Robert Rice to Edwin Beal Regarding Phelps Dodge Grievances with Grievances, March 30, 1941; 4.
      - Farnsworth Local 902 Grievance Committee Meeting Minutes, March 25, 1943; 5.
      - Perfection Wage List, March 1943; 6.
      - Fred Gardner to James Matles Regarding Factionalism, April 2, 1943; 7.
      - John Gojack to Matles Regarding Fort Wayne Dairy Equipment Contracts, August 9, 1943; 8.
      - Gojack to A. N. Townsen Regarding VanArnam, August 31, 1943; 9.
      - Elizabeth Moore to Emspak Regarding Tokheim Organization with Leaflets, June 30, 1945; 10.
      - Gojack to David Ratner Regarding Finances with David Scribner Memo to Emspak, January 17, 1952; 11.
      - Ruth G. to Ratner Regarding Officers, January 25, 1954; 12.
      - Resolution Regarding Marshall Plan, 13.
  - Local 903
    - Local 903 Contracts, 1937-1943 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Local 903 Officers Lists, January 23, 1937-April 16, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Local 903 Membership Resolutions, July 1942-July 1944 (Box 4, Folder 51)
      - Resolution Regarding Red-baiting, July 1942; 1.
      - Resolution Regarding Wages, July 1944; 2.
    - Local 903 Incoming Correspondence, August 7, 1936-December 12, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 52)
      - Julius Emspak to Charles Watson Regarding Organization, August 7, 1936; 1.
      - Emspak to Watson Regarding Finances and RCA Strikes, December 14, 1936; 2.
      - Emspak to Watson Regarding Per Capita, December 14, 1936-January 13, 1937; 3-4.
      - Emspak to Gerald Schooley, April 16, 1938; 5.
      - Emspak to Robert Arney Regarding Per Capita, October 13, 1938; 6.
      - Emspak to Clem Grabner Regarding Singer Strikes, May 22, 1939; 7.
      - Emspak to Local 903 Regarding Per Capita, August 25, 1939; 8.
      - Emspak to Grabner Regarding Contracts, April 6, 1940; 9.
      - Emspak to Clarence Schweyer Regarding Air King Strikes and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, September 20, 1940; 10.
      - Emspak to Schweyer Regarding Retirees, November 13, 1940; 11.
      - Emspak to Schweyer Regarding UE News, March 10, 1941; 12.
      - Emspak to Schweyer Regarding Local 903 Constitutions, October 27, 1941; 13.
      - Emspak to Schweyer Regarding Bonding, November 3, 1941; 14.
      - Emspak to Schooley Regarding Mine Mill Strikes, March 3, 1932; 15.
      - Emspak to Schweyer Regarding Political Action, September 24, 1942; 16.
      - Emspak Telegram to Schweyer Regarding Wages, October 16, 1942; 17.
      - Emspak to Grabner Regarding Bowser Grievances, April 15, 1944; 18.
      - Emspak to Robert Arney Regarding Dues and Veterans, February 16, 1945; 19.
      - Emspak to Arney Regarding Finances, June 21, 1946; 20.
      - Emspak to Arney Regarding Per Capita, January 8, 1947; 21.
      - Emspak to Hoyte Thomas Regarding Finances, May 18, 1954; 22.
      - Emspak to Arney Regarding Finances, May 18, 1954; 23.
      - Emspak to Jesse Moots Regarding Finances, December 12, 1955; 24.
    - Local 903 Incoming Correspondence, October 1, 1938-April 10, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 53)
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Robert Arney Regarding Constitutions, April 10, 1952; 1.
      - James Matles to Howard Delo Regarding Local 902 and Reorganization, October 1, 1938; 2.
      - Matles to Clarence Schweyer Regarding Bowser Company Union, July 29, 1940; 3.
      - Matles to Schweyer Regarding Bowser Company Union with July 30, 1940, Mollie Schultz to Matles, August 6, 1940; 4.
      - Matles to Arney Regarding Staff Members, February 4-17, 1942; 5-6.
      - Matles Telegram to Clem Gardner, July 7, 1947; 7.
      - David Scribner to Schweyer Regarding Labor Analyst, May 5, 1944; 8.
      - Scribner to Schweyer Regarding Wayne Pump Jurisdiction, January 25, 1945; 9.
      - Alice Smith to Schweyer Regarding War Labor Board, September 19, 1944; 10.
      - Smith to Schweyer Regarding War Labor Board and Wayne Pump, September 20, 1944; 11.
    - Local 903 Outgoing Correspondence, July 16, 1937-June 27, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 54)
      - Robet Arney to UE Regarding Strike Fund, August 27, 1938; 1.
      - Arney to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, October 22, 1938; 2.
      - Arney to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, January 24, 1942; 3.
      - Arney to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, Dues and Veterans, February 12, 1945; 4.
      - Arney to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, December 2, 1946; 5.
      - Arney to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, December 9, 1946; 6.
      - Arney to Emspak Regarding United Auto Workers-American Federation of Labor, and International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalries, and Wayne Pump, August 9, 1951; 7.
      - Arney to Emspak Regarding Constitution, April 3, 1952; 8.
      - Arney to Emspak Regarding Wayne Pump Strikes, May 12, 1953; 9.
      - Arney to Emspak Regarding Unemployment and Finances, May 27, 1955; 10.
      - Arney to James Matles Regarding Finances and Wayne Pump Negotiations, June 2, 1955; 11.
      - Arney to Emspak Regarding Finances, July 13, 1955; 12.
      - Homer Beeching to Emspak Regarding Officers, May 31, 1939; 13.
      - Beeching to Emspak Regarding Political Action, August 26, 1939; 14.
      - Harold Berkheiser to Emspak Regarding Local 705 Strikes, February 15, 1937; 15.
      - Berkheiser to Emspak Regarding Officers, July 16, 1937; 16.
      - Clem Grabner to Emspak Regarding Wayne Pump Contracts, April 2, 1940; 17.
      - Grabner to Matles Regarding Wayne Pump Officers, March 15, 1941; 18.
      - Grabner Telegram to Emspak Regarding Bowser Strikes, April 7, 1944; 19.
      - Grabner Telegram to Matles Regarding Wayne Pump Negotiations, July 4, 1947; 20.
      - Grabner to Homer Capehart Regarding Civil Rights and Political Action, January 9, 1950; 21.
      - Arney to Emspak Regarding Buttons, June 16-27, 1955; 22-23.
      - Grabner to William Jenner Regarding Civil Rights and Political Action, January 9, 1950; 24.
      - Grabner to Edward Kruse Regarding Civil Rights and Political Action, January 9, 1950; 25.
      - Rita Little to Matles Regarding Officers, June 11, 1942; 26.
    - Local 903 Outgoing Correspondence, April 9, 1938-November 23, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 55)
      - Homer Marachand to Hosken Damon Regarding Bowser Negotiation with Navy Memo, February 21, 1942; 1.
      - Jesse Motts to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances and Suspension, November 23, 1955; 2.
      - James Nash to Emspak Regarding Membership Maintenance, February 1, 1945; 3.
      - Nash to James Matles Regarding Wayne Pump Negotiations, October 26, 1945; 4.
      - Nash Telegram to Emspak Regarding Taft-Hartley, June 27, 1947; 5.
      - Elwood Parent to Emspak Regarding Military Personnel with April 15, 1942, Stella Memo to Emspak, April 13, 1942; 6.
      - Gerald Schooley to Emspak Regarding Constitution, April 9, 1938; 7.
      - Schooley to Emspak Regarding Union Label Shoes, February 4, 1939; 8.
      - Clarence Schweyer to Emspak Regarding Officers, January 29, 1940; 9.
      - Schweyer to Matles Regarding Tokheim and Staff Members, May 15, 1940; 10.
      - Schweyer to Emspak Regarding Air King Strikes and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, August 30, 1940; 11.
      - Schweyer to Emspak Regarding Retirees, November 5, 1940; 12.
      - Schweyer to Emspak Regarding UE News, March 3, 1941; 13.
      - Schweyer to Emspak Regarding Finances, January 3, 1942; 14.
      - Schweyer to Emspak Regarding Retirees, July 29, 1942; 15.
      - Schweyer to Emspak Regarding United Mine Workers of America, May 27, 1943; 16.
      - Schweyer to UE Regarding Address Change, April 26, 1944; 17.
      - Schweyer to Emspak Regarding Analyst, April 27, 1944; 18.
      - Schweyer to Emspak Regarding War Labor Board and Wages, September 19, 1944; 19.
      - Schweyer to Emspak Regarding Wayne Pump Jurisdiction, January 16, 1945; 20.
      - Schweyer to Walter Reuther Regarding United Auto Workers Inter-union Rivalry and Local 935, May 4, 1948; 21.
      - Schweyer to Local 901 Regarding Factionalism with May 7, 1948, Schweyer Letter to Emspak, May 1948; 22.
      - Schweyer to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Deportation, August 26, 1948; 23.
      - Schweyer to Driscoll Regarding Phelps Dodge Strikes, May 26, 1949; 24.
      - Schweyer to Kirk Regarding Phelps Dodge Strikes, May 26, 1949; 25.
      - Schweyer to Emspak Regarding Factionalism, November 28, 1949; 26.
    - Local 903 Outgoing Correspondence, December 10, 1936-May 19, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 56)
      - Victor Somers to UE Regarding Finances, September 7, 1938; 1.
      - Hoyte Thomas to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism and Officers with March 4, 1952, Fitzgerald Letter to John Gojack, February 28, 1939; 2.
      - Thomas to Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism and Officers, June 26, 1952; 3.
      - Thomas to Julius Emspak Regarding Strikes Fund, November 6, 1952; 4.
      - Thomas to Emspak Regarding Strike Fund, December 11, 1952; 5.
      - Thomas to Emspak Regarding Local 1114 Strikes, September 3, 1953; 6.
      - Thomas to Emspak Regarding Wayne Pump and Inter-union Rivalry, March 19, 1954; 7.
      - Thomas to Emspak Regarding Inter-union Rivalry and Unemployment, May 14, 1954; 8.
      - Thomas to Emspak Regarding Finances, May 19, 1954; 9.
      - Charles Watson to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, December 10, 1936; 10.
    - Local 903 Reports of Financial Secretary, December 1936-July 1938 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Local 903 Monthly Statement, July-November 1936 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Local 903 Notice of Delinquency, November 1937 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Local 903 Wayne UE Victory News, June 17-July 3, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Local 903 Seniority-Saver, April 22-28, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Local 903 News, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Local 903 Pamphlets, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 63)
      - What UE Means to Wayne Pump Workers, 1954; 1.
    - Local 903 Leaflets, June 14, 1940-May 15, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 64)
      - Notices, NLRB Election, June 14, 1940; 1.
      - IAM Dictatorship Builds Treasury By Selling Jobs, 1941; 2.
      - Membership Unities Regarding Wayne Pump Negotiations, January 13, 1952; 3.
      - Allen Dangles Sucker Bait Regarding Wayne Pump Negotiations, January 21, 1953; 4.
      - Fact For UE Members Regarding Wayne Pump Negotiations, January 27, 1953; 5.
      - Negotiating Committee Letter to Stewards Regarding Wayne Pump, February 9, 1953; 6.
      - No Progress Regarding Wayne Pump Negotiations, February 20, 1953; 7.
      - A Well Organized Strike Means A Short Or No Strike Regarding Wayne Pump Negotiations, 1953; 8.
      - Wayne Pump Notified, March 15, 1954; 9.
      - Inside the IAM, April 12, 1954; 10.
      - UE All the Way, May 15, 1954; 11.
      - A Comparison Regarding International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, 12.
      - The IAM-AFL Constitution, 13.
      - We Quote Regarding International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, 14.
      - UE Election Notes Regarding International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, 15.
      - Attention Regarding Firings, 16.
      - Unemployed Bulletin, 17.
      - Inside the IAM, 18.
      - Company Union Application Regarding Tokheim, 19.
      - Special Meeting, 20.
    - Local 903 Embezzlement, July 27-December 13, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 65)
      - Ed Bunting to Julius Emspak, July 27, 1938; 1.
      - Bertha Scott to Emspak, July 27, 1938; 2.
      - Emspak to Scott with Local 903 Statement, July 30, 1938; 3.
      - Emspak to Scott with Local 903 Financial Statement, August 21, 1938; 4.
      - Scott to Emspak, September 29, 1938; 5.
      - Oliver Switzer to Emspak, December 2, 1938; 6.
      - Emspak to Switzer, December 10, 1938; 7.
      - Switzer to Emspak, December 12, 1938; 8.
      - Emspak to Switzer, December 13, 1938; 9.
    - Local 903 Tokheim, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 66)
      - C. C. Oberly to All Shop Employees, October 13, 1939; 1.
      - Memo, November 29, 1939; 2.
      - Arthur Meloan to Oberly, November 30, 1939; 3.
      - Oberly to Meloan, December 1, 1939; 4.
      - Oberly to All Shop Employees, December 1, 1939; 5.
      - Meloan to Robert Cowdrill, 1939; 6.
    - Local 903 Bowser Grievances, April 7-May 1, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 67)
      - Julius Emspak to John Gojack, April 7, 1944; 1.
      - Gojack to Emspak, April 10-May 1, 1944; 2-3.
    - Local 903 Per Capita, November 14-20, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 68)
      - Julius Emspak to Elizabeth Moore, November 14, 1944; 1.
      - Moore to Emspak, November 20, 1944; 2.
    - Local 903 Bowser Factionalism, June 13-October 9, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 69)
      - C. L. Teeter to Albert Fitzgerald, June 13, 1944; 1.
      - John Gojack to Fitzgerald, June 20, 1944; 2.
      - Robert Kirkwood to Julius Emspak, June 21, 1944; 3.
      - Gojack to Emspak, October 9, 1944; 4.
    - Local 903 1945 Tokheim Orientation, January 11-October 10, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 70)
      - Elizabeth Moore to Julius Emspak, January 11, 1945; 1.
      - Empsak to Moore, January 18, 1945; 2.
      - Robert Dyer to Robert Rice, October 2, 1945; 3.
      - Rice to Robert Kirkwood, October 10, 1945; 4.
      - Rice to Dyer, October 10, 1945; 5.
    - Local 903 Wayne Pump Strike and Inter-union Rivalry, February 23-June 19, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 71)
      - John Gojack to Albert Fitzgerald, February 23, 1953; 1.
      - Memo, April 28, 1953; 2.
      - Julius Emspak to Borton Miller, April 28, 1953; 3.
      - Emspak to John Gojack, April 28, 1953; 4.
      - Gojack to James Matles, May 13, 1953; 5.
      - Questionnaire, May 29, 1953; 6.
      - Gojack to Matles, June 19, 1953; 7.
    - Local 903 Casner Lay-off, January 18-June 3, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 72)
      - A. C. Casner to Albert Fitzgerald, January 18, 1954; 1.
      - Fitzgerald to Casner, January 25, 1954; 2.